(spirited upbeat music)
♪ I'm saying all the things
that I know you'll like ♪
♪ Making good conversation ♪
♪ I gotta handle you just right ♪
♪ You know what I mean ♪
♪ I took you to an intimate restaurant ♪
♪ Then to a suggestive movie ♪
♪ There's nothing left to talk about ♪
♪ Unless it's horizontally ♪
♪ Let's get physical, physical ♪
♪ I wanna get physical ♪
♪ Let's get into physical ♪
♪ Let me hear your body
talk, your body talk ♪
♪ Let me hear your body talk ♪
♪ Let's get physical, physical ♪
♪ I wanna get physical ♪
♪ Let's get into physical ♪
♪ Let me hear your body
talk, your body talk ♪
♪ Let me hear your body talk ♪
♪ I've been patient, I've been good ♪
♪ Tried to keep my hands on the table ♪
♪ It's gettin' hard, this holdin' back ♪
♪ You know what I mean ♪
♪ I'm sure you'll understand
my point of view ♪
♪ We know each other mentally ♪
♪ You gotta know that
you're bringin' out ♪
♪ The animal in me ♪
♪ Let's get physical, physical ♪
♪ I wanna get physical ♪
♪ Let's get into physical ♪
♪ Let me hear your body
talk, your body talk ♪
♪ Let me hear your body talk ♪
♪ Let's get physical, physical ♪
♪ I wanna get physical ♪
♪ Let's get into physical ♪
♪ Let me hear your body
talk, your body talk ♪
♪ Let me hear your body talk, ah ♪
(spirited upbeat music continues)
♪ Oh, let's get physical, physical ♪
♪ I wanna get physical ♪
♪ Let's get into physical ♪
♪ Let me hear your body
talk, your body talk ♪
♪ Let me hear your body talk ♪
♪ Let's get animal, animal ♪
♪ I wanna get animal ♪
♪ Let's get into animal ♪
♪ Let me hear your body
talk, your body talk ♪
♪ Let me hear your body talk ♪
♪ Your body talk ♪
(spirited upbeat music fades)